The Gilbert and Lila Silverman Fluxus Collection Archives
The Museum of Modern Art, Publisher
- Series V: George Maciunas Papers, 1900-2012
  - Subseries V.A: Correspondence
    - Subseries V.A.2: Photocopy Correspondence to and from George Maciunas
      - Ken Friedman, 1966-1973, undated; Correspondence from Maciunas; transcripts. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.45)
      - Gallery 669, 1968; Correspondence from Maciunas. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.46)
      - Ludwig Gosewitz, 1977; Correspondence to Maciunas. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.47)
      - Raoul Hausmann, 1962; Correspondence to Maciunas. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.48)
      - Jon Hendricks, 1977; Correspondence from Maciunas. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.49)
      - Dick Higgins, 1962-1963, undated; Correspondence from Maciunas. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.50)
      - Armin Hundertmark, 1976; Correspondence from Maciunas; transcripts. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.51)
      - Toshi Ichiyanagi, undated; Maciunas's notes. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.52)
      - Mr. Kaplan, 1963; Correspondence from Maciunas. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.53)
      - Allan Kaprow, undated; Maciunas's notes. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.54)
      - Milan Knžk, 1966-1975; Correspondence from Maciunas; transcripts. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.55)
      - Alison Knowles, 1971, undated; Correspondence from Maciunas; Maciunas's notes; transcripts. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.56)
      - Takehisa Kosugi, undated; Maciunas's notes. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.57)
      - Shigeko Kubota, undated; Maciunas's notes. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.58)
      - Dan Lauffer, undated; Correspondence from Maciunas. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.59)
      - Jackson Mac Low, undated; Maciunas's notes. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.60)
      - Leokadia Maciunas, 1977; Correspondence to and from Maciunas. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.61)
      - Joan Mathews, 1975-1978; Correspondence to Maciunas. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.62)
      - David Mayor, 1972, undated; Correspondence from Maciunas. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.63)
      - David Mayor, 1971-1973; Correspondence to Maciunas. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.64)
      - New School, 1963; Correspondence from Maciunas. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.65)
      - Claes Oldenburg, undated; Maciunas's notes. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.66)
      - Nam June Paik, 1962-1963, undated; Correspondence from Maciunas; Maciunas's notes. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.67)
      - Ben Patterson, 1963, undated; Correspondence from Maciunas. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.68)
      - Giancarlo Politi, undated; Correspondence from Maciunas. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.69)
      - Max Porch, undated; Correspondence from Maciunas. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.70)
      - Terry Riley, undated; Maciunas's notes. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.71)
      - Harry Ruh, 1975-1976; Correspondence from Maciunas. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.72)
      - Takako Saito, 1977, undated; Maciunas's notes; correspondence from Maciunas; transcripts. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.73)
      - Tomas Schmit, 1963; Correspondence from Maciunas; transcripts. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.74)
      - Tomas Schmit, 1963-1964; Correspondence from Maciunas. (Box 139, Folder V.A.2.75)
      - Arturo Schwartz, undated; Correspondence from Maciunas. (Box 140, Folder V.A.2.76)
      - Paul Sharits, 1966-1970; Correspondence from Maciunas; transcripts. (Box 140, Folder V.A.2.77)
      - Stuart Sherman, 1977-1978; Correspondence to Maciunas. (Box 140, Folder V.A.2.78)
      - Mieko Shiomi, 1972-1975, undated; Correspondence from Maciunas; Maciunas's notes. (Box 140, Folder V.A.2.79)
      - Hans Sohm, undated; Correspondence from Maciunas. (Box 140, Folder V.A.2.80)
      - Daniel Spoerri, 1963, undated; Correspondence from Maciunas. (Box 140, Folder V.A.2.81)
      - Yuji Takahashi, undated; Maciunas's notes. (Box 140, Folder V.A.2.82)
      - Ben Vautier, 1963-1965, undated; Maciunas's notes; correspondence from Maciunas; transcripts. (Box 140, Folder V.A.2.83)
      - Ben Vautier, 1966-1976, undated; Correspondence from Maciunas; transcripts. (Box 140, Folder V.A.2.84)
      - Wolf Vostell, 1965, undated; Correspondence from Maciunas. (Box 140, Folder V.A.2.85)
      - Robert Watts, 1963, undated; Correspondence from Maciunas. (Box 140, Folder V.A.2.86)
      - Robert Watts, 1963-1966, undated; Correspondence from Maciunas; transcripts. (Box 140, Folder V.A.2.87)
      - Mike Weaver, 1964; Correspondence from Maciunas. (Box 140, Folder V.A.2.88)
      - Clemens Weiler, undated; Correspondence from Maciunas. (Box 140, Folder V.A.2.89)
      - Robert Whitman, undated; Maciunas's notes. (Box 140, Folder V.A.2.90)
      - Emmett Williams, 1962-1963, undated; Correspondence from Maciunas; transcripts. (Box 140, Folder V.A.2.91)
      - Emmett Williams, 1962-1963, undated; Correspondence from Maciunas; Maciunas's notes; transcripts. (Box 140, Folder V.A.2.92)
      - La Monte Young, 1962-1963, undated; Correspondence from Maciunas. (Box 140, Folder V.A.2.93)
      - Various recipients, 1966-1975; Correspondence from Maciunas. (Box 140, Folder V.A.2.94)
  - Subseries V.B: Working Files
    - Subseries V.B.1: Working Files
      These files are comprised of material formerly belonging to George Maciunas, though the archivist cannot guarantee this for every individual item, due to the complex custodial history of the material. This subseries contains 3 types of folders: created by Maciunas, created by Hendricks, and created by the archivist. There is no original order; the archivist arranged these folders alphabetically. This subseries should be understood as a group of original material organized, culled, and used by Hendricks.
      Most folders here were created by Maciunas. A large portion of the George Maciunas estate material acquired both through partial purchase of the estate and from Jonas Mekas consists of Maciunas's personal files, envelopes labeled by him and called here "working files." For the most part, Hendricks maintained the contents and internal order of these files; nonetheless, some individual materials were removed and filed elsewhere. These removals are occasionally but not always documented. Most, but not all, folders found empty here can be presumed to have been originally empty. The presence of an original Maciunas "working file" is designated by quotation marks around the folder's title. When a folder's title differs from its contents, the archivist supplied a pertinent title in square brackets in addition to Maciunas's title.
      The second type of folder found here contains items from the Maciunas estate foldered and labeled by Hendricks, and inserted into this run of working files. Hendricks's folder titles have been maintained where appropriate, and are not marked by any special punctuation.
      The third type of folder found here consists of material gathered by the archivist and inserted into this run, including items misfiled in other parts of the Collection. These folders are indicated by square brackets around the title.
      These files contain a great deal of working material: clippings, public-domain images, negatives, photographs, and sketches for Fluxus and other projects. These are organized either thematically or by project. When such working material (mainly negatives, photographs, and labels) was identified as a specific Fluxus work by Jon Hendricks's notes, and found individually, not as part of a grouping, it was transferred to the Museum collection. Researchers wishing to view working material for a specific work should contact the study center of the Department of Prints and Illustrated Books.
      - "1250 Box", undated; Research, notes, working material. (See also: "Historical boxes.") (Box 141, Folder V.B.1.1)
      - 8 O'Clock Art Forums, 1970; Flyer. (Box 141, Folder V.B.1.2)
      - "Ace Space", 1970, undated; 1 postcard Ace Space - Maciunas (8/7/1970); newsletters and documents. (Box 141, Folder V.B.1.3)
      - Ace Space Company, 1970; Flyer for SPACE ATLAS, 3 copies. (Box 141, Folder V.B.1.4)
      - "Ads", Working material. (Box 141, Folder V.B.1.5)
      - African Sculpture, 1 photograph of mask. (Box 141, Folder V.B.1.6)
      - [Aktual Art International], 1967; Flyer and photograps from exhibition Aktual Art International, San Francisco Museum of Art (5/2-21/1967), organized by Jeff Berner. (Box 141, Folder V.B.1.7)
      - "Akumulatory", 1974-1976; Ephemera. (Box 141, Folder V.B.1.8)
      - "Albrecht, Dietrich", 1972; 1 TLS Albrecht D. - Maciunas regarding project for documenta 6. Also includes empty folder ("Albrecht - Dietrich"). (Box 141, Folder V.B.1.9)
      - "All group", 1968, undated; Publications from ALL (musical group directed by Alan Sondheim). (Box 141, Folder V.B.1.10)
      - [An Anthology] "Misc. texts", undated; Mechanical (working material) for 2nd edition of An Anthology. (Box 141, Folder V.B.1.11)
      - An Anthology, 1971; 1 TLS Richard W. Beebe - Maciunas regarding order (11/17/1971). (Box 141, Folder V.B.1.12)
      - [An Anthology], 1970; 1970 edition. Inventory #s: 05234 (Box 141, Folder V.B.1.13)
      - "Anatomy", undated; Working material. (Box 141, Folder V.B.1.14)
      - "Anatomy - negs", undated; Working material. (Box 141, Folder V.B.1.15)
      - "Eric Anderson" [Andersen], undated; List of works and ephemera by Eric Andersen (from the artist?), including Archiv Sohm information sheets (for Happening & Fluxus catalogue chronology, 1970). (Box 141, Folder V.B.1.16)
      - "Eric Anderson" [Andersen], 1968, undated; Works by Eric Andersen. (Box 141, Folder V.B.1.17)
      - Eric Andersen, 1972, undated; Works and ephemera. (Box 141, Folder V.B.1.18)
      - "Andrul photos", undated; 9 photographs (working material). (Box 141, Folder V.B.1.19)
      - "Animals", undated; Working material. (Box 141, Folder V.B.1.20)
      - Anonymous, undated; Unidentified sketches, texts, and correspondence. (Box 141, Folder V.B.1.21)
      - Anonymous / Portraits / negatives for Fluxus I, undated; Working material. (Box 141, Folder V.B.1.22)
      - "Apparatus - / Chemical / Mechanical", undated; Working material. (Box 141, Folder V.B.1.23)
      - "Arc-do Da-a/u del", undated; Da-a/u del magazine, 2 copies. (Box 141, Folder V.B.1.24)
      - [Architectural drawings], undated; Drawings by Maciunas. (Box 411, Folder V.B.1.25*)
      - [Architectural photographs], undated; 1 of 3 folders. Mostly photographs of European architecture. From a photographic paper box. (Box 141, Folder V.B.1.26)
      - [Architectural photographs], undated; 2 of 3 folders. Mostly photographs of European architecture. From a photographic paper box. (Box 141, Folder V.B.1.27)
      - [Architectural photographs], undated; 3 of 3 folders. Mostly photographs of European architecture. From a photographic paper box. (Box 142, Folder V.B.1.28)
      - Architecture, 1970; 1 TLS C. Micmaker - Maciunas (3/14/1970). (Box 142, Folder V.B.1.29)
      - "Architecture", undated; Working material (original folder missing). (Box 142, Folder V.B.1.30)
      - John Armleder, 1974; 1 empty envelope mailed to Fluxus (11/3/1974). (Box 142, Folder V.B.1.31)
      - "Art & Urban Resources / Clocktower / PS-1", 1976, undated; Ephemera. (Box 142, Folder V.B.1.32)
      - Art Workers Newsletter, 1971; Vol. 1, no. 2. (Box 142, Folder V.B.1.33)
      - The Arts Council of Great Britain, 1970; Exhibition loan request (3/24/1970). (Box 142, Folder V.B.1.34)
      - "Aspen projects.", undated; Notes, preparations and working material for Aspen no. 8, Fluxus issue of magazine (1970). Includes ALS Ed Ruscha - Dan Graham (4/30/1968). (Box 142, Folder V.B.1.35)
      - Aspen, undated; Invoice for Maciunas's work on Aspen no. 8, Fluxus issue of magazine (1970). Silverman #s: 254 Inventory #s: 00571 (Box 142, Folder V.B.1.36)
      - "Aspen - Jackson McLow", 1969; Concerns "Young Turtle Asymmetries," Jackson Mac Low's contribution to Aspen no. 8, Fluxus issue of magazine (1970). Includes copy of work and TLS Jackson Mac Low - Maciunas (11/10/1969). (Box 142, Folder V.B.1.37)
      - D. Atchley (ace space co), undated; Mailing to Maciunas from Dana Atchley. (Box 142, Folder V.B.1.38)
      - "Audiences, crowds, dinners, feasts.", undated; Working material. (Box 142, Folder V.B.1.39)
      - Avant Garde Festival, 1972; Program (1972). (Box 142, Folder V.B.1.40)
      - "Back of head", undated; 1 photograph (working material). (Box 142, Folder V.B.1.41)
      - "Backworks", 1976; Accounting; lists of works received for sale. (Box 142, Folder V.B.1.42)
      - "Bak, Imre", 1974, undated; Works and correspondence mailed to Maciunas. (Box 142, Folder V.B.1.43)
      - Larry Baldwin, 1966; Empty envelope (8/17/1966). (Box 142, Folder V.B.1.44)
      - "Banana", 1972, 1976; Postcards and newsletter from Anna Banana. (Box 142, Folder V.B.1.45)
      - banco, 1974; 1 piece ephemera. (Box 142, Folder V.B.1.46)
      - "Barbara's cook book", undated; Working material and recipes contributed by artists for Fluxus cookbook by Barbara Moore. Avquired from Jonas Mekas. (Box 142, Folder V.B.1.47)
      - "Baruchello, Gianfranco", 1968, 1978; 2 exhibition catalogues. (Box 142, Folder V.B.1.48)
      - "Battisti, Carlo", 1976; Ephemera. (Box 142, Folder V.B.1.49)
      - Carlo Battisti, undated; Ephemera. (Box 142, Folder V.B.1.50)
      - Beatles, 1970; Copy of check to Maciunas from "B/O Beatles & Co" (11/6/1970). (Box 142, Folder V.B.1.51)
      - Beau Geste Press, 1974, undated; Ephemera. (Box 142, Folder V.B.1.52)
      - "Belgium", 1971; Ephemera from the Galerie Yellow. (Box 142, Folder V.B.1.53)
      - Peter Below, 1975; Mailing to Maciunas, including ephemera and other documents. (Box 142, Folder V.B.1.54)
      - [Berlin], 1976; Materials related to 1976 trip to Berlin for New York, downtown Manhattan, SoHo exhibition at Akademie der Knste, Berlin. Includes programs and "souvenir trash" (food labels). Acquired from Jonas Mekas. Accession #s: 94.18 (Box 143, Folder V.B.1.55)
      - "Berlin Trip" 1 of 7, 1976; Materials collected during 1976 trip to Berlin for New York, downtown Manhattan, SoHo exhibition at Akademie der Knste, Berlin. Includes notes for "Berlin souvenir box," travel documents, Fluxus concert program (9/3/1976). (Box 143, Folder V.B.1.56)
      - "Berlin Trip" 2 of 7, 1976; Food labels. (Box 143, Folder V.B.1.57)
      - "Berlin Trip" 3 of 7, 1976; Includes ephemera, maps, newspapers. (Box 143, Folder V.B.1.58)
      - "Berlin Trip" 4 of 7, 1976; Material removed from "Berlin Trip" folder. Includes notes on itinerary and accounting; ALS Charles Dreyfuss - Maciunas; Fluxcabinet note. (Box 143, Folder V.B.1.59)
      - "Berlin Trip" 5 of 7, 1976; Material removed from "Berlin Trip" folder. 3 ALS from Leokadia Maciunas. (Box 143, Folder V.B.1.60)
      - "Berlin Trip" 6 of 7, 1976; Material removed from "Berlin Trip" folder. Plans and notes by Maciunas for Flux Labyrinth; TLS Ren Block - Maciunas (7/7/1976) regarding planning. (Box 143, Folder V.B.1.61)
      - "Berlin Trip" 7 of 7, 1976; Material removed from "Berlin Trip" folder. Notes, program and ephemera for Flux-Harpsichord concert; "was ist wann?" booklet for "Kulturinformationen aus Berlin" (9/1/1976 - 11/31/1976). (Box 143, Folder V.B.1.62)
      - "Berliner Festspiele", 1973; Correspondence with Maciunas. (Box 143, Folder V.B.1.63)
      - Jeff Berner, undated; Fold-out, "Anyone whose eyes light upon this image" (Box 143, Folder V.B.1.64)
      - Jeff Berner, undated; 1 TL to Maciunas. Acquired from Jonas Mekas. (Box 143, Folder V.B.1.65)
      - "Jeff Berner", 1966; Correspondence and mailed works. (Box 143, Folder V.B.1.66)
      - "Jeff Berner", 1965-1966; Correspondence and mailed works. (Box 143, Folder V.B.1.67)
      - "Beuys, Joseph", 1970-1971; Ephemera. (Box 143, Folder V.B.1.68)
      - Joseph Beuys, 1970; Ephemera. (Box 143, Folder V.B.1.69)
      - Biographical Data, undated; Curriculum vitae (2 copies) and notes by Maciunas. (Box 143, Folder V.B.1.70)
      - "Black Thumb press", 1966-1968; Ephemera and mailings. (Box 143, Folder V.B.1.71)
      - "Boat trip - maps / notes - compl.", undated; Planning for world-wide boat trip (possibly "Circumnavigation of the world with 85ft schooner, 1976-80"; see newsletter in V.F.15). (Box 143, Folder V.B.1.72)
      - Boats, undated; Promotional materials for boats and boat trips. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.73)
      - "Boats, airplanes", undated; Working material. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.74)
      - "Bodies", undated; Working material. Accession #s: 94.18 (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.75)
      - Books, 1970; Includes book-of-the-month-club documents. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.76)
      - "Bottles", undated; Working material (original folder missing). (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.77)
      - [Box of Smile], 1971; Order of materials for Yoko Ono's Box of Smile(1971). (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.78)
      - "Boxes", undated; News clipping, "Boxes as Art Form Shown At a Retrospective in Paris." (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.79)
      - "Boxes, suitcases", undated; Working material (original folder missing). (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.80)
      - "Boyd, Donald", 1976; Ephemera. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.81)
      - Boynton Studio Shop, 1970; Audio equipment circulars. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.82)
      - "Brain Fame" ('Brain Frame'), undated; Various documents connected to the Brain Frame Co. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.83)
      - "Brecht, George", 1971, undated; Includes "The Brunch Museum;" ephemera. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.84)
      - "George Brecht - unused", undated; Various documents. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.85)
      - George Brecht, 1969, 1973; Exhibition catalogues. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.86)
      - [George Brecht], 1972; 1 TLS George Brecht - Maciunas (4/5/1972). (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.87)
      - Brown University, undated; 1 TLS Stewart A. Baker - Maciunas. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.88)
      - Jean Brown, undated; Notes. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.89)
      - "Jean Brown", 1975-1977; Correspondence; "Instructions for visitors to Jean Brown archives" (9/1/1977); notes; sketches; photographs of Jean Brown's house and art storage. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.90)
      - [Jean Brown], 1974; 1 postcard Jean Brown - Maciunas (8/16/1974). (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.91)
      - "Brown, Sparky", 1966; Correspondence. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.92)
      - "Brown, Trisha", 1976, undated; Chronology; news clippings. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.93)
      - Trisha Brown and company, 1974; 1 flyer. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.94)
      - "BT", 1967; Bit magazine (May 1967, no. 2). Features photographs and report on Fluxus "festival of free expression" in Turin. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.95)
      - Buildings, 1971, undated; Real estate and travel clippings; architecture ephemera. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.96)
      - [Burglary Flux Kit], undated; 1 sheet with notes and sketches; label. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.97)
      - Eugenia S. Butler (Gallery), 1967; 1 flyer. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.98)
      - "John Cage", undated; "Notes on meeting with John Cage concerning G. Maciunas Chart," extensive notes about John Cage's works and career. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.99)
      - John Cage, 1971; Ephemera. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.100)
      - "California, misc.", 1970-1973; Correspondence; ephemera. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.101)
      - "Calligraphy - Asiatic", undated; Working material. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.102)
      - "Canada, misc.", 1972, undated; Correspondence. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.103)
      - Car, 1971, 1976; Vehicle permit stub (1976) and automotive parts catalogue. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.104)
      - "Carpets", undated; 1 negative (working material) (for Implosions product?). (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.105)
      - Luciano Caruso, 1974; Ephemera. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.106)
      - Tullio Catalano, undated; Booklet with autograph note mailed to Maciunas. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.107)
      - "Cavellini, G.A.", undated; Photocopies of texts about painters from 25 quadri della Collezione Cavellini. (Box 144, Folder V.B.1.108)
      - "Cayc", 1974-1975; 2 publications by CAYC (centro de arte y communicacion). (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.109)
      - Cayc, 1973-1975; Ephemera. (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.110)
      - "Giancarlo Celli", 1967; News clipping. (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.111)
      - Chain letters, undated; Correspondence. (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.112)
      - "Chart", undated; Type for the "Diagram of Historical Development of Fluxus" (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.113)
      - "Chart / completed mtl." 1 of 5, 1966, undated; Preparatory material for Maciunas's "Diagram of Historical Development of Fluxus and Other 4 Dimentional [sic], Aural, Optic, Olfactory, Epithelial and Tactile Art Forms." This folder includes correspondence from Per Kirkeby, Eric Andersen, and Arthur Køpcke regarding their own work and Fluxus history. (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.114)
      - "Chart / completed mtl." 2 of 5, 1971, undated; Preparatory material for Maciunas's "Diagram of Historical Development of Fluxus and Other 4 Dimentional [sic], Aural, Optic, Olfactory, Epithelial and Tactile Art Forms." This folder includes extensive notes, curriculum vitae of Fluxus artists, ephemera, and correspondence. (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.115)
      - "Chart / completed mtl." 3 of 5, undated; Preparatory material for Maciunas's "Diagram of Historical Development of Fluxus and Other 4 Dimentional [sic], Aural, Optic, Olfactory, Epithelial and Tactile Art Forms." This folder includes the "Expanded Arts Diagram" from Film Culture - Expanded Arts, no. 43 (1966); notes. (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.116)
      - "Chart / completed mtl." 4 of 5, undated; Preparatory material for Maciunas's "Diagram of Historical Development of Fluxus and Other 4 Dimentional [sic], Aural, Optic, Olfactory, Epithelial and Tactile Art Forms." This folder includes ephemera, notes. (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.117)
      - "Chart / completed mtl." 5 of 5, undated; Preparatory material for Maciunas's "Diagram of Historical Development of Fluxus and Other 4 Dimentional [sic], Aural, Optic, Olfactory, Epithelial and Tactile Art Forms." This folder includes ephemera, notes. (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.118)
      - "Chiari, Giuseppe", 1973-1974; Ephemera. (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.119)
      - Giuseppe Chiari, undated; 1 postcard to Maciunas. (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.120)
      - "Christo", 1977; Excerpt from The New Yorker with article about Running Fence(3/28/1977). (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.121)
      - Christo, undated; 1 note from Christo ("merry christmas"). (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.122)
      - Circumnavigation of the globe, undated; 1 map sketch. (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.123)
      - "Citron", undated; Photographs. (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.124)
      - "City - interiors - bldgs.", undated; Working material. (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.125)
      - "Clockfaces - stat", undated; Photocopy of working material. (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.126)
      - "Colored acetate - / sunglasses", undated; Working material. (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.127)
      - "Concerts 1962-1966", 1962-1970; Ephemera. (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.128)
      - "Concerts, Events etc.", 1969, undated; Includes ephemera from Non-art, Vrit-art, Anti-art Festival. (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.129)
      - "Concrete poetry", 1965, undated; Includes Les Lettres no. 34 (1965). (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.130)
      - "Cooper Union - / Furniture.", undated; Working material and typescript, "The Virgin Enthroned, and The Lamb of God with Symbols of the evangelists, A stylistic comparison" by Maciunas. (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.131)
      - Fletcher Copp, 1974; 1 postcard to Maciunas (6/21/1974). (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.132)
      - "Cornell, Joseph", 1975-1976; Newsclippings; flyer for films of Joseph Cornell designed by Maciunas. (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.133)
      - Correspondence, 1974-1975; Various mail (including ephemera, bills and junk mail) to Maciunas. Acquired from Jonas Mekas. (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.134)
      - Correspondence, 1973-1974; Various mail (including ephemera, bills and junk mail) to Maciunas. (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.135)
      - [Correspondence], 1973-1974, undated; Various mail to Maciunas. (Box 145, Folder V.B.1.136)